Guide to the Chi Phi Fraternity, Xi Chapter records, 1875-1996
Chi Phi Fraternity, Xi Chapter records, 1875-1996
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Chi Phi Fraternity, Xi Chapter. Records, 1875-1996
37-4-1990
Chi Phi (Fraternity). Xi Chapter (Cornell University).
5 cubic ft.
Scrapbooks, record books, correspondence.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Records of Chi Phi Fraternity, Xi Chapter.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes scrapbooks regarding Chi Phi activities; Craigielea Memorial Education Fund, Inc. correspondence, 1947-1979, and file book, 1983-1985; material on the chapter house; Chapter House Association file books, 1979-1987; checkbooks; pictures of Chi Phi plaques; published history CHRONICLES OF CHI PHI, by Dr. Theodore B. Appel, 1939, and revised version, 1993; and other records of Chi Phi, Xi Chapter at Cornell University. Also renovation plans for the chapter house by William Henry Miller and Arthur N. Gibb, ca. 1895.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Appel, Theodore Burton, 1871-1937.; Craigielea Memorial Education Fund.; Cornell University--Societies, etc.; Cornell University--Students.
Subjects:
Greek letter societies.
Form and Genre Terms:
Scrapbooks.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Scrapbook, 1875-1885 (Box 1)
- Scrapbook, ca.1890-1906 (Box 1)
- Scrapbook, 1892-1898 (Box 1)
- Craigielea Memorial Educational Fund, Inc. Correspondence, Mar. 1947-June 1959 (Box 2)
- Chi Phi New Building Special File, 1951-1969 (Box 2)
- Book: Record of Bonds: Chi Phi Chapter House Association, 1900 (Box 2)
- Book of Chi Phi Checks, 1904-1911 (Box 2)
- Book of Chi Phi Checks, 1912-1916 (Box 2)
- Chi Phi New Building Program Alumni Responses, 1968 (Box 3)
- Craigielea Memorial Scholarship Grant, n.d. (Box 3)
- Chi Phi Memorial Plaques: Pictures, n.d. (Box 3)
- Chi Phi Renovation Feasibility Study, Magnitude of Cost Estimate, June 7, 1968. Anton J. Egner & Associates (Box 3)
- Chi Phi Chapter House Association correspondence, Nov. 1960-June 1979 (Box 3)
- Chi Phi Chapter House Association correspondence, Nov. 1960-June 1979 (Box 4)
- Chapter House Association file books, 1979-1985 (Box 5)
- Craigielea Educational Fund, Inc., 1983-1985 (Box 5)
- Chapter House Association file books, Craigielea Educational Fund, Inc. records, and Craigielea Memorial Scholarship Grant records, 1979-1987 (Box 6)
- Craigielea Educational Fund, Inc. (Box 7)
- Craigielea Memorial Fund seal, MU-2477 (Box 8)
- Oversize items (Mapcase-folder 1)
  Renovation plan is restricted